[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Woody and Buzz Light Year are characters from this video game based on a Disney movie.", "correct_answer": "Toy Story", "incorrect_answers": ["Jump In!", "Camp Rock", "Planet 51"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Sudanese/American basketball player and activist, 77 (2.31 m) tall, managed to block 397 shots during the 1985-1986 season, thus setting a rookie record.", "correct_answer": "Manute Bol", "incorrect_answers": ["Yao Ming", "Swede Holbrook", "Wilt Chamberlain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This green vegetable is number one on the list of foods that contain agents preventing cancer. The list contains about 30 such agents.", "correct_answer": "Broccoli", "incorrect_answers": ["Cabbage", "Spinach", "Lettuce"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Talladega Nights: The Ballad of Ricky Bobby, Rickys wife, Carley, says, If we wanted two wussies, we would have named them Billy Bob and Ethel.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the colors of the national flag of Sweden?", "correct_answer": "Blue and yellow", "incorrect_answers": ["White and blue", "White and red", "Red and yellow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which process involves rotating of champagne bottles and gradually moving them to a neck-down orientation?", "correct_answer": "riddling", "incorrect_answers": ["none of these", "secondary fermentation", "disgorging"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where did Sheriff Bart take off for at the end of the film Blazing Saddles?", "correct_answer": "Nowhere Special", "incorrect_answers": ["New York", "Hollywood", "Paris France"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the following an example of: Madam, Im Adam?", "correct_answer": "Palindrome", "incorrect_answers": ["Perambulation", "Personalisation", "Personification"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The catfishes Physailia pellucida and Kryptopterus bicirrhis, found in the mid-waters of Southeast Asia, use what kind of camouflage?", "correct_answer": "Transparency", "incorrect_answers": ["Change their colour", "Mimic algae", "Mimic poisonous fish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If an orbiting body is revolving around its parent body in a perfectly circular path at a distance of 1,000,000,000 kilometers with an orbital velocity of 15 km/s, how long is its year in Earth years?", "correct_answer": "13.28", "incorrect_answers": ["11.39", "27.42", "7.23"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What rapper and singer voices Moto Moto the Hippopotamus in the 2008 animated comedy Madagascar: Escape 2 Africa?", "correct_answer": "will.i.am", "incorrect_answers": ["Pharrell Williams", "Wyclef Jean", "Kanye West"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Latin expression means actions speak louder than words?", "correct_answer": "facta non verba", "incorrect_answers": ["quid edere  posseum", "mei capelli sunt  flagrantes", "non rape me si placet"]}]